[
  {
    "question": "Greet someone! Say 'hi!'",
    "choice1": "oi!",
    "choice2": "ciao!",
    "choice3": "tchau",
    "choice4": "Bem-vindo",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'Good morning'?",
    "choice1": "Bom dia",
    "choice2": "Boa noite",
    "choice3": "Boa tarde",
    "choice4": "Eu vou",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'Yes'?",
    "choice1": "Não",
    "choice2": "Sim",
    "choice3": "Tchau",
    "choice4": "Amigo",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'No'?",
    "choice1": "Não",
    "choice2": "Sim",
    "choice3": "Eu",
    "choice4": "Gato",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'I am not'?",
    "choice1": "eu não sou",
    "choice2": "eu não posso",
    "choice3": "ele tem um gato",
    "choice4": "ela tem um menino",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Greet someone! Say 'hi!'",
    "choice1": "oi!",
    "choice2": "ciao!",
    "choice3": "tchau",
    "choice4": "Bem-vindo",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'Good morning'?",
    "choice1": "Bom dia",
    "choice2": "Boa noite",
    "choice3": "Boa tarde",
    "choice4": "Eu vou",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'Yes'?",
    "choice1": "Não",
    "choice2": "Sim",
    "choice3": "Tchau",
    "choice4": "Amigo",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'No'?",
    "choice1": "Não",
    "choice2": "Sim",
    "choice3": "Eu",
    "choice4": "Gato",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'I am not'?",
    "choice1": "eu não sou",
    "choice2": "eu não posso",
    "choice3": "ele tem um gato",
    "choice4": "ela tem um menino",
    "answer": 1
  }
]
